{
    "id": "116cd70104644a9dabc95a2965b21f73",
    "title": "Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He was driving ……………………… and crashed into the car in front.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "carefully",
                "carelessly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "67dff465f91547abbadd63cf0050d833"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. the tiger appeared from nowhere.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Suddenly",
                "Slowly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "95bc259dd2c2442ca8f4e808f681fc50"
        },
        {
            "question": "The rain poured ………………………. and we took shelter under a tree.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "heavily",
                "lightly",
                "slightly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f70e98ca020e4216b468f06ba25af87e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher told a funny story and the children laughed ……………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "loudly",
                "softly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "520aadc50b74425485522570c85a8fa2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dancers performed ……………………. and we all clapped.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gracefully",
                "clumsily"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "afc261954c194d14a8b40b4c280577c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you shouting ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "loudly",
                "quietly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "72212cfd2e87433ba25d3522a5a47773"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has a golden voice. She sings ……………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "beautifully",
                "badly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "011a6a4b475a4b4593292a80c09cfd90"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t take a decision …………………………… Think it over for sometime.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hastily",
                "slowly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7c395d08d77d4f549fd55b208d0873c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The soldiers fought so …………………….. that the enemy troops fled.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bravely",
                "timidly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d0f2bad04259449c9d91c49d12c5c7d9"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you walk ………………………. you will not reach there in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "slowly",
                "slow",
                "fast"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "10130d723c254ad49b964a95d205e1b1"
        }
    ]
}